(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
AZKi対バン企画 LAST V STANDiNG vol.3 #LVS3 【GUEST：MaiR】
AZKi Joint Live Project: LAST V STANDiNG vol.3 #LVS3 【GUEST: MaiR】
ピンポンパンポーン
Ding-dong-ding-dong
本日は、AZKi対バン企画『LAST V STANDiNG vol.3』をご覧いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for watching AZKi's joint live project, "LAST V STANDiNG vol.3" today.
開演に先立ちまして、ご来場のお客様にお願い申し上げます。
Before the show starts, we have a few requests for the audience.
本放送は配信限定のライブとなります。
This broadcast is a stream-exclusive live performance.
皆様それぞれの環境で、近所迷惑にならない程度に、応援をお願いいたします。
Please support us in your respective environments as long as it doesn't disturb your neighbors.
また、撮影はスクリーンショットのみ可能となります。
Additionally, only screenshots are allowed for photography.
ぜひライブの様子を、ハッシュタグ「#LVS3」で投稿してください。
Please post about the live using the hashtag "#LVS3".
ダイブ、サーフ、突然床になるなどの危険行為は禁止となります。
Dangerous acts such as diving, surfing, or suddenly becoming the floor are prohibited.
危険行為により怪我をする可能性もございますので、
There is a possibility of injury due to dangerous acts,
安全な観覧にご理解ご協力をお願いいたします。以上です！
so we ask for your understanding and cooperation for safe viewing. That's all!
よくできました！
Well done!
読めたー！よかったー！
I could read it! Thank goodness!
はい、ということで、今日はね、なんと二人で、やっちゃいます、ライブ！
Yes, so today, the two of us will be doing a live together!
やっちゃいますよ！ついに来ましたよ！
We're doing it! It's finally time!
MaiRちゃんと...Mai-Az...Mai-Az...
With MaiR-chan... Mai-Az... Mai-Az...
あ、ちょっとじゃあ、やろう、あれ。
Oh, wait, let's do it, that thing.
円陣を組みたいと思います。皆さんよろしいでしょうか？
I'd like to do a huddle. Everyone, are you ready?
はい、オッケーです。
Yes, okay.
それでは、掛け声は『Mai-Az』でいきましょうか。
Then let's go with the "Mai-Az" shout.
はい。
Yes.
では、お願いします！
Then, please!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
Mai-Az! Mai-Az! Oh!
ということで、開演まで、ちょっと待っててね！
So, please wait a little longer until the show starts!
AZKi対バン企画 LAST V STANDING vol.3
AZKi Versus Project: LAST V STANDING vol.3
零れ光る あなたの声
Overflowing and shining, your voice
暗い闇を照らす
Illuminating the dark darkness
LVS3始まりました！盛り上がっていきましょう！
LVS3 has started! Let's get excited!
乾いた空を越えて巡る
Traveling across the dry sky
記憶の色は 褪せて溶け滲んだ
The colors of memories have faded, melted, and blurred
冷たい空気刻む 時の針が
The hands of time carving the cold air
孤独の淵へ誘う
Inviting me to the edge of loneliness
交わした思いは消えないよ
The feelings we exchanged will never disappear
誓いあった未来で会うため
To meet in the future we promised each other
満ちた波に浮かぶ星は
The stars floating on the full waves
遠い夢を映し燃えていく
Reflecting distant dreams and burning away
僅か触れた指の熱を
The heat of the fingers that barely touched
呼び覚ませる幻
A phantom that can be awakened
逃れられない運命でも
Even if it's an inescapable fate
かけがえのない存在に救われ
Saved by an irreplaceable existence
煌めく風を掴むように
As if to catch the sparkling wind
崩れる世界
The crumbling world,
信じた
I believed
鼓動と揺れる瞳の奥
A heartbeat and the depths of swaying eyes
忘れないよ 透明な涙
I won't forget, the transparent tears
静寂に包まれた
Enveloped in silence
蒼い月 祈りを込める
The blue moon, I offer a prayer
ただ一つ不変の愛
The only unchanging love
抱きしめて踏み出した
Embracing it, I stepped forward
零れ響くあなたの声
Spilling and echoing, your voice
生きる意味を繋ぐぬくもり
The warmth that connects the meaning of life
二人ここで重ねた日は永遠に
The days we spent together here will be forever
焼いてる
I'm burning
はいということで、あらためまして、こんあずきー！
All right! Once again, Kon-AZKi!
こんあずきー！
Kon-AZKi!
こんめあー！
Kon-Mea!
はい、今日はですね、AZKi対バン企画 LAST V STANDiNG Vol.3ということで
Well, today is the AZKi collaboration event, LAST V STANDiNG vol.3!
皆さんお越しいただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you all for coming!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
では自己紹介していきましょうか。
Shall we introduce ourselves?
皆さんこんあずき、AZKiです！
Hello everyone, Kon-AZKi, I'm AZKi!
今日はめあちゃんとのね、もうね待ちに待った対バン...
I've been looking forward to this collab with Mea-chan for so long...
...楽しみにまいりましたので
...and I'm so happy to be here today.
どうぞ最後まで、最後まで！
Please watch until the very end, the very end!
最後まで見てほしいな、でよろしくお願いします！
I hope you enjoy it all. Thank you!
いぇーい！
Yay!
そしてそして！
And and!
さあやってまいりました、世界のめ...
Now, here she is! The world's Me—
あ、あ...
Ah, ah...
だーーー！
Dahhh!
まあ今日は聞けた。
Well, I got to hear it today.
対バンということで、まあ二人ならではなところとか
Since it's a collab, we want to show things only the two of us can do,
あとまあ、お互いの自分らしさみたいなのをね
and also express our own individualities...
思いっきりね届けられたらな、ぶつけながら！
...to the fullest while challenging each other!
ぶつけたり、抱き合ったり。
Clashing and hugging.
していきたいと思います！
That's how we're going to do it!
皆さんこの、この立ち姿だけで我ら、いや、すごいシナジー感じません？
Don't you feel a great synergy just from the way we're standing here?
やばく、もうさ、めっちゃさ写真とか撮りまくってたもんね。
It's crazy. We were taking so many photos earlier, weren't we?
見てください皆さん。ちょっと撮影タイム、はかどる、はかどる！
Look, everyone. It's time for a photo session. So efficient!
撮影タイム開始
Photo session begins
ちょっと見て。見とれちゃった。撮影タイム。
Just look. I'm captivated. Photo time.
皆さん見とれてませんか？ 嬉しい。
Are you all captivated too? I'm so happy.
そう、すごい赤とね青のこの二人のコントラストめちゃくちゃ良くないですか？
The contrast between the red and blue of us two is great, isn't it?
いぇい、いぇいいぇい、いぇいいぇい！
Yay! Yay, yay, yay, yay!
ということで、ここからどうしますか？
So, what shall we do now?
まあそうですね、ここからはソロパート...
Well, let's move on to the solo parts.
お、ソロパートやりますか！
Oh, solo parts! Let's do it!
まずはAZKiちゃんからお願いします！
Starting with AZKi-chan, please!
行かせていただきますので、皆さんついてきてくださいね！
I'll be going first, so everyone, please follow along!
頑張ってね！
Good luck!
はい、頑張りまーす！
Okay, I'll do my best!
はいということで、ここからはね、お互いにソロパートを歌っていきたいと思います。
All right, so from here on, we'll each be singing our solo parts.
ではまずは、AZKiの、AZKiのソロから行きたいと思います。
First up is AZKi's solo part.
それではこの曲から聴いてください。「Creating world」
Please listen to this song first. "Creating world".
Creating world
この扉の向こう側が 未知の可能性だわ
Beyond this door lies unknown possibilities
今を動かせるの
I can move the present moment
暗闇を手探りで 不安と焦燥の中
Groping through the darkness, amidst anxiety and frustration
こぼれる光を見た
I saw the overflowing light
手を伸ばした この先は君のものだから
I reached out, because the future belongs to you
時を超えて 繋がるよ 心が今
Transcending time, our hearts are connecting now
創造するのは 私のストーリー
What I create is my story
声を聞かせて 君を知りたいから
Let me hear your voice, because I want to know you
輝かせよう 新しい世界
Let's make it shine, a new world
生まれた意味を見つけるのさ
I'll find the meaning of being born
全てが始まるこの場所で
In this place where everything begins
声が枯れるまで 叫んで
Shout until your voice runs dry
言葉に傷つき 誰か 悲しみが凍えるのは
The reason someone's sadness freezes from hurtful words
弱いからじゃない
Isn't because they are weak
勇気がここにあるから かき消されちゃダメなんだ
Because courage is here, it mustn't be drowned out
君は君のままでいい
You can just be yourself
声をあげて 私たちの歌は壊れない
Raise your voice, our song won't break
...たって
...even if I am.
伝えるよ ココロを今
I'll tell you my heart right now.
共鳴するの 私のストーリー
My story resonates.
名前を呼んで そばにいるから
Call my name, because I'm by your side.
音を奏でよう 新しい世界
Let's play the sound, a new world.
キミに出会うために 生きていくんだ
I'm living to meet you.
この場所が 奇跡だから
Because this place is a miracle.
リアルを超えて 繋ぐよ
Going beyond reality, I'll connect us.
さあ
Now!
夜は深く 眠りに落ちて
The night falls into a deep sleep,
やがて光が 世界を照らすよ
And eventually light will illuminate the world.
キミと出会えたこと 意味を見つけたのさ
Meeting you, I found the meaning.
共に分かち合って 生きたい
I want to live sharing it with you.
創造するの 私のストーリー
I'll create my story.
声を聞かせて キミを知りたいから
Let me hear your voice, because I want to know you.
開拓するの 新しい世界
I'll pioneer a new world.
嘘じゃないんだ キミとのストーリー
It's not a lie, the story with you.
全てが始まる この場所で
Everything begins in this place.
歌を歌い続けるよ
I will keep singing.
Ah
Take me to Heaven
宇宙の最後の日 奏でる最後の歌
Thinking about the last day of the universe, the last song to be played,
のこと考えてる 知らないうちに
without even knowing it.
引き継ぐ空気みたいに むしろ呪いみたいに
Like the air I breathe in, or rather like a curse,
いびつなほど かけがえなく そこにある
distorted as it may be, it's there, irreplaceable.
そう 息が止まる その瞬間まで
Yes, until the moment my breath stops,
この音楽に 溺れてたいの
I want to be drowned in this music.
Take me
音のない世界じゃ この体はきっと
In a world without sound, this body surely...
Eternity
ほんの少しだって 生きてちゃいられない
I can't live for even a little while.
だからもう
So now...
Take me to heaven 連れていって あのメロディが私を
Take me to heaven, take me away, that melody leads me.
Eternity
まるで永遠みたいな音で呼んで
Call me with a sound that's just like eternity.
どうか Take me to heaven
Please, take me to heaven.
一人で夜を越す日 信じる相手もいない
Days spent alone through the night, with no one to believe in.
どうしようもないくらい 長い夜に
In a night so long that there's nothing I can do.
一生みたいなプレイリスト 迷路の出口いつも
A playlist like a whole life, always the exit to the maze.
放り投げている 決してなくさぬように
I keep throwing it out, so as never to lose it.
私は最後の日 抱える最初の答え
On my last day, the first answer I hold...
はきっとまだ 胸の中 心臓のように
...is surely still in my chest, like a heart.
引き継ぐ空気みたいに むしろ呪いみたいに
Like the air I breathe in, or rather like a curse,
いびつなほど かけがえなく そこにある
distorted as it may be, it's there, irreplaceable.
もう 何も他に望まないと誓って
I swear I don't want anything else anymore,
一つだけ願いが 叶うのならば
if only one wish could come true.
もし 息が止まるその日は
If the day my breath stops...
この音楽に埋もれたいの
I want to be buried in this music
"Take me"
音のない世界じゃこの体きっと
In a world without sound, this body surely...
"Eternity"
ほんの少しだって生きちゃいられない
...couldn't live for even a little while.
だから Oh
So, oh...
"Take me to heaven"
連れて行ってあのメロディで私を Oh
Take me away with that melody, oh...
"Eternity"
たとえ無限の孤独の真ん中だとしても
Even if I'm in the middle of infinite loneliness...
"Stairway to Heaven"
それでいいの "Take me to heaven"
That's fine, "Take me to heaven"
それがいいの "Take me to heaven"
That's what I want, "Take me to heaven"
"Take me"
音のない世界じゃこの体きっと
In a world without sound, this body surely...
"Eternity"
ほんの少しだって生きちゃいられない
...couldn't live for even a little while.
だから Oh
So, oh...
"Take me to heaven"
連れて行ってあのメロディで私をそこへ
Take me away with that melody to that place
"Stairway to Heaven"
それでいいの "Take me to heaven"
That's fine, "Take me to heaven"
それがいいの "Take me to heaven"
That's what I want, "Take me to heaven"
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
ということで、2曲続けてお送りしました。「Creating World」「Take me to heaven」でした。
And so, I've just performed two songs in a row. They were "Creating World" and "Take me to heaven."
いかがでしたか？
How was it?
お水飲んでもいいですか？
May I have some water?
ライブお決まり事、お水を飲む。
A concert tradition: drinking water.
お水、飲みました！
I've finished my water!
お水ありがとう。みんなお水、お水スタンプありがとね。
Thanks for the water. Thanks for all the water stamps, everyone.
ありがとうございます。すごい、すごい大量のお水が溢れんばかりに。ありがとうございます。
Thank you. Wow, there's such a massive amount of water, it's almost overflowing. Thank you.
お水助かる。お水助かります。ありがとうございます。700円ありがとうございます。
The water helps. It really helps. Thank you. And thank you for the 700 yen.
はい、ということでですね、この感じでどんどん行きたいと思うんですけれども。
Alright, so, I want to keep this momentum going, but...
ここからですね、ま、ちょっとAZKiのちょっと可愛い、可愛い感じのAZKiを、ちょっと。溺れるほどの水、ありがとうございます。
From here on, well, I'd like to show you a bit of a cute... a cute side of AZKi. Thanks for enough water to drown in.
えっと、可愛い感じのAZKiを、見せていきたいと思います！
Um, I'm going to show you a cute side of AZKi!
ということで、この曲聞いてください。「リアルメランコリー」
So, please listen to this song: "Real Melancholy."
答えを教えて リアルメランコリー
Tell me the answer, Real Melancholy
みんなで、イェーイ！
Everyone, yay!
イェーイ！
Yay!
体と感情が交差する 正しい自分は何？
Body and emotions intersect, what is the "true" me?
二と三を繋いで交差する 世界は一つじゃない
Connecting two and three as they intersect, the world is not just one
リネクトファボの数字 増えていく
The numbers of retweets and favorites keep increasing
表向き正論振りかざして首を締める
Brandishing superficial logic and strangling myself
私の生きる world は 自分の手で選ばせてよ
Let me choose the world I live in with my own hands
真夜中のメランコリー 生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
Midnight melancholy, a reborn identity
この身がこの変が痛いよ
This body, this part here hurts
上辺っ面の泣きストーリー
A superficial tear-jerker story
そして可愛らしいフェイス
And a lovely face
私は 私は
I am, I am
誰かにとって
To someone
変わるの？
Will I change?
イェー！
Yeah!
理想と現実が交差する
Ideal and reality intersect
正しい私は何？
What is the "correct" me?
再生回数が落ちていく
The view count is dropping
世界はどこも同じだ
The world is the same everywhere
キャラ属性カテゴリーライズされていく
Character attributes are being categorized
誰かに決めつけられたような流行はやだな
I hate trends that seem decided by someone else
私のやりたいことは
What I want to do
自分の手で決めさせてよ
Let me decide with my own hands
真夜中のメランコリー
Midnight melancholy
生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
A reborn identity
この身が この辺が 痛いよ
My body, this area, hurts
嘘じゃないこの想い
This feeling is not a lie
同じじゃない詰まる想い
These choked-up feelings aren't the same
私は 私は
I am, I am
誰かにとって
To someone
変わるの？
Will I change?
流行りも好き どっちも欲しい
I like trends too, I want both
矛盾の自問自答繰り返してく
Repeating a contradictory monologue
何番目のコピーじゃないと
Unless I'm some numbered copy
永遠の夜を超えていく
Going beyond the eternal night
未知なる世界へ
To an unknown world
1人目の手を繋いで
Holding the hand of the first person
真夜中のメランコリー
Midnight melancholy
生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
A reborn identity
だけどね私は1人じゃない
But you know, I'm not alone
どこかの世界の君へ
To you, somewhere in the world
私と似てる気持ちの君へ
To you, who feels similar to me
エールを送るよ
I'll send you a cheer
私のために
For my sake
真夜中のメランコリー
Midnight melancholy
生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
A reborn identity
この身が この辺が 痛いけど
My body, this area, hurts, but
どこかの世界の君へ
To you, somewhere in the world
私と似てる気持ちの君へ
To you, who feels similar to me
エールを送るよ
I'll send you a cheer
君と私のために
For you and for me
イェー！
Yeah!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
どんどん行くよ！
Let's keep going!
フェリシア
Felicia
どうして気づいてしまったの
Why did I notice?
熱くなる頬に
On my burning cheeks
隠しきれない戸惑い
Confusion I can't hide
ぎこちない距離
An awkward distance
あやふやな視線
Vague gazes
揺れる心バレないように
Lest my shaking heart be discovered
人知れず響く胸の鼓動
The heartbeat that echoes secretly
呼吸さえままならないのに
Even though I can hardly breathe
きっとどこかで願っているんだ
I'm surely wishing somewhere
終わりのない時間を
For a time without an end
恋の始まりは誰も知らない
No one knows the beginning of love
私だけの宝物
My very own treasure
少しでも言葉にカタチにしたら
If I put it into words or shape even a little
日だまりのような笑顔も
A smile like a sunny spot
土砂降りの泣き顔も全部
And a crying face like a downpour, all of it
無くしてしまいそうで
It feels like I might lose them
もしも一つだけ叶うのならば
If only one wish could come true
ただ君のすぐ隣で
Simply by your side
過ぎてゆく季節眺めていたい
I want to watch the passing seasons
溢れそうなほどの想いは
These feelings that are about to overflow
胸の奥にしまい込んだ
I've tucked them away deep in my heart
二人の声は空に吸い込まれてく
Our voices are being swallowed into the sky
どんなに考えてみても
No matter how much I think about it
一ミリたりとも
Not even a single millimeter
終わらない本当のことが
The truth that never ends
頭の中を
Inside my head
覗けたらなんて
If I could take a peek
四六時中 ぼんやりして
Day and night, feeling dazed
そよ風がどこからともなく
A gentle breeze from out of nowhere
おともなく君をさらっていく
Silently taking you away
その時まで愛おしくして
Until then, cherish it
誰が何を投げるの？
Who is throwing what?
恋の行き先は誰も知らない
No one knows where love goes
私だけの宝物
My very own treasure
変わらない夕暮れに甘えてる
Indulging in the unchanging sunset
重なる二人の影に
In our overlapping shadows
静かにはしゃいだ気持ちは
Feelings that quietly frolicked
壊れてしまいそうさ
Seem like they're about to break
いつか大人になってしまうならば
If we're to become adults someday
何よりただ二人
More than anything, just the two of us
振り向いた先で笑っててほしい
I want us to be smiling when we look back
どこまでも募る思いは
The feelings that keep growing
いつまでもここにあるんだ
Will always be here
二人の声は空に
Our voices in the sky
溶けてしまう
Will melt away
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
わあー、いっぱいハートと拍手ありがとう！
Wow, thank you for all the hearts and applause!
見えてますよ 見えてますよ
I can see you, I can see you
見えてますよ
I can see you
はい、ということで お水を飲みます
All right, I'm going to drink some water
お水飲んでね
Drink your water too
はい
Okay
AZKiのソロパートも いよいよラスト2曲となっております
AZKi's solo part is finally down to the last two songs
皆さん まだまだ まだまだ盛り上がっていけますか？
Everyone, are you ready to keep getting even more hyped?
水 大量にありがとね
Thanks for all the water!
まだまだ盛り上がっていけますかー？
Are you ready to keep getting even more hyped?
声だしてー！
Let me hear your voices!
ちょっと、ちょっと時差があるけど
There's a bit of a delay, but...
イエーイ！
Yeah!
じゃあね みんなにもね 歌ってもらいたいなと思います
Now, I'd like for all of you to sing along too
みんな ウォーウォーウォーウォー してもらいたいなと思います
I want everyone to go "Woah-woah-woah-woah"
ということで 次はこの曲！
So, next is this song!
『発光体ソーラーサイクル』！
"Hakkou Kaisou Solar Cycle"!
みんな行くよ！
Everyone, here we go!
せーの！
One, two!
ウォー ウォー ウォー ウォー...
Woah woah woah woah...
壊してなくなった壁は
The walls that were broken and gone
いつかあったことも忘れて
Have forgotten they ever existed
壊すためのその拳は
Those fists meant for breaking...
何を作るの？
...what will they create?
離れた星の住人が
Dwellers of a distant star
わけも知らず
Without knowing why
またぶつかり合っている
Are clashing once again
ステージのバックライトは
The backlights on the stage
背中に感じるだけじゃない
Are not just felt on the back
次に立つ誰かのために
For someone standing here next
輝いている
They are shining
今すぐ世界は変わらないけど
The world won't change right away, but
11年後の君に歌うよ
I'll sing for you 11 years from now
今日も夜空は こんなに冷たいのに
The night sky is so cold tonight, and yet...
この街の灯は いつも熱い
...the city lights are always warm
一人ひとりのストーリーが
Each and every person's story
あふれているから
Is overflowing here
Because it's overflowing
Say Hello! 届け未来的 Show Time!
Say Hello! Deliver a futuristic Show Time!
自信持ってもっと激しく遊べ
Play more fiercely with confidence
My sister
今も The Dream!!
Even now, The Dream!!
全部叶えていこう
Let's make it all come true
夢見る力が地上を照らせば
If the power of dreaming illuminates the earth
誰かの好きがつながって So Miracle
Someone's 'love' connects and it's So Miracle
またいつか花開くよ
It will bloom again someday
Soracycle! みんなできるよねー！
Soracycle! Everyone can do it, right!
Woah-woah-woah-woah...
もっと！
More!
Woah-woah-woah-woah...
OK!
ぼくら自分と世界の時差を混同しがちで
We tend to confuse the time lag between ourselves and the world
世界が大人になってると勘違いして
Mistakenly thinking the world is becoming an adult
あるときループから放り出されて
One day, being thrown out of the loop
変わり映えしない日々に戸惑う
Bewildered by the unchanging days
誰かの夢が連鎖してゆくのは
The chain reaction of someone's dream
自由を縛る鎖じゃなくて
Is not a chain that binds freedom
少しずつでもまだ見ぬ世界
Even if little by little, a world not yet seen
見えたらいいよね
It would be nice if we could see it
Say Hello! 響け宇宙的 Big Wave!
Say Hello! Resonate with a cosmic Big Wave!
瞳輝かせた君が好きさ
I like you with your eyes sparkling
My sister
今も The Dream!!
Even now, The Dream!!
いつも全身全霊
Always with all my heart and soul
磁力線の向こう側目指して
Aiming for the other side of the magnetic field lines
一瞬の閃光が永遠になって Spark
A momentary flash becomes eternity and Spark
この世界を変えてくよ
Changing this world
Soracycle
みんな今日は LVS3 来てくれてありがとねー！
Everyone, thank you for coming to LVS3 today!
うわー、コメントもハートもサイリウムもいっぱいありがとう！もっと盛り上がっていきましょう！
Wow, thank you for all the comments, hearts, and psylliums! Let's get even more excited!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
懐かしいことが心地いいとき
When nostalgic things feel comfortable
新しいことは辛いこと
New things are painful things
それでも新しい
Still, something new
明日が見たい
I want to see tomorrow
Say Hello! 届け未来的 Show Time!
Say Hello! Deliver a futuristic Show Time!
自信持ってもっと激しく遊べ
Play more fiercely with confidence
My sister
今も The Dream!!
Even now, The Dream!!
全部叶えていこう
Let's make it all come true
夢見る力が地上を照らせば
If the power of dreaming illuminates the earth
誰かの好きがつながって So Miracle
Someone's 'love' connects and it's So Miracle
またいつか花開くよ Soracycle
It will bloom again someday, Soracycle
僕らの今が君を動かして
Our present moves you
またいつか花開くよ Soracycle
It will bloom again someday, Soracycle
Woah-woah-woah-woah...
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Woah-woah-woah-woah...
ありがとう！
Thank you!
AZKi、最後は
AZKi, for the last song...
MaiRちゃんの曲を歌わせてもらいます！
I'll sing MaiR-chan's song!
みんな聞いてね、ドリームトリップ！
Everyone listen, Dream Trip!
頑張ってたって落ち込んだ日もあるでしょ
Even if you were working hard, there must be days when you felt down
ほら探してみよう 欠片集めて
Look, let's go find them, gathering the pieces
いつだって今だって みんながくれた言葉
Always, even now, the words everyone gave me
意地っ張りな僕を変えてくれた
Changed the stubborn me
部屋の隅で抱えてた
Held in the corner of the room
伝えたい歌届けて
Deliver the song I want to convey
のように空に浮かぶあの願いは
Like those wishes floating in the sky
世界動かす秘めた力
The hidden power that moves the world
ありがとう 走り出した
Thank you, started running
走りだした
I've started running
夢をのせて
Carrying my dreams
坂をこえて
Over the hill
信じ合えるさ
We can believe in each other
迷わない！
I won't hesitate!
そう思っていた
That's what I thought
君を照らす
Shining on you
光になると信じて
Believing I'll become the light
ありがとう
Thank you
これからだよ
It's just starting
つれてくから
Because I'll take you with me
夢の先へ
Beyond the dream
君がいるなら
If you are here
叶わないはずないよなんてね
There's no way it won't come true, or so I say
調子のっちゃって
Getting carried away
もいーよね☆
Is okay, right?☆
いつだって 今だって
Always, even now
この背中を押したのは
What pushed me forward
そばで笑いかけてくれた君だ
Was you, smiling by my side
描いていた
In that place
あの場所には
I had pictured
僕ではない
Someone
誰かがいた
Other than me was there
滲んだ先に見えた光を待っていた
I was waiting for the light seen through the haze
弱虫の独り占めした軌跡
The trajectory a coward kept all to themselves
ありがとう
Thank you
走りだした
I've started running
夢をのせて
Carrying my dreams
坂をこえて
Over the hill
信じ合えるさ
We can believe in each other
迷わない！そう思っていた
I won't hesitate! That's what I thought
君を照らす 光になると信じて
Believing I'll become the light that shines on you
ありがとう
Thank you
君がいるなら
If you are here
叶わないはずないよなんてね
There's no way it won't come true, or so I say
調子のっちゃって
Getting carried away
もいーよね☆
Is okay, right?☆
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
ということでね、MaiRちゃんのオリジナル曲
And so, I sang MaiR-chan's original song
「ドリームトリップ」を歌わせていただきましたー！
'Dream Trip'!
ということは、ということは！
Which means, which means!
ここで、MaiRちゃんを呼び込みたいと思います！
I'd like to invite MaiR-chan out here now!
みんな、いいですか？みんなコメントの準備できてますか？
Is everyone ready? Are you all ready to comment?
「MaiRちゃん」で呼びたいと思いますよー。
I'm going to call for 'MaiR-chan'.
はい、いきますよー。
Okay, here we go.
せーの！
One, two!
MaiRちゃーーん！
MaiR-chaaan!
はーーい！
Heeey!
MaiRだよー！MaiRだよー！
It's MaiR! It's MaiR!
MaiRだよー！
It's MaiR!
はい、ということでMaiRちゃんに再び登場していただきましたー！
Alright, so MaiR-chan is back on stage with us!
お疲れ様ー！
Good job!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いや、めっちゃ良かった！
No, it was amazing!
なんかすごいね、袖にね、MaiRちゃんが見えて...
Yeah, it was great, I could see MaiR-chan in the wings...
ちょっと、ちょろちょろしてたでしょ？
I was peeking a little bit, wasn't I?
すごいね、なんか一緒に盛り上がって
It was awesome, she was getting hyped up with me,
こうやって、ノリノリで聞いて、聞いてくれてた。
like this, grooving along while listening.
嬉しすぎて、もう。ありがとう！
I was just so happy. Thank you!
ありがとうございます。ということで、ここからは！
Thank you very much. So, from here on!
MaiRちゃん、ソロバトンタッチして。
MaiR-chan, I'll hand over the baton for your solo.
はい！
Yes!
もうみんなね、もう力強いMaiRちゃんのこのターン
Everyone, let's get fully hyped for
全力で盛り上がっていきたいと、思います！
MaiR-chan's powerful turn!
ちょっと、また始まりみたい。
Wait, it feels like the beginning again.
いや、盛り上げて。盛り上げ隊長。
No, get them hyped. Hype captain.
盛り上げ隊長。
Hype captain.
はい、じゃあMaiRちゃん、意気込みどうですか？
Alright, MaiR-chan, how are you feeling about this?
いや、まあね、あの、AZKi先生から...
Well, you know, from AZKi-sensei...
ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って, なんですか？
Wait a minute, wait a minute, what was that?
なんですか？
What?
AZKiちゃんじゃないの？
Isn't it AZKi-chan?
いや、AZKi先生、あれ、AZKi先生ですよね、皆さん。
No, AZKi-sensei, wait, it's AZKi-sensei, right everyone?
ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って。何、何？
Wait, wait, wait. What, what?
はい、いいですか、お願いします。
Okay, are you ready? Please go ahead.
AZKi先生から、まあみんなのコメントから...
From AZKi-sensei, and from everyone's comments...
あ、AZKi先生からね、たくさん...
Ah, I've received a lot from AZKi-sensei...
今、なんていうんだろう、元気もらったので。
Right now, how should I say it, I've received energy.
パワー、パワー。
Power, power.
そう、パワー、パワーもらったので。
Yes, I've received power, power.
もう上乗せして、次のね、自分のターンも飛ばしていきたいと思います！
I'm going to add to that and blast through my next turn!
やったー！
Yay!
もう最後まで見るしかない！
You just have to watch until the end!
見てくれ！
Please watch!
はい、じゃあメアちゃん、頑張ってね！
Okay, then, MaiR-chan, good luck!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい！
Yes!
えー...
Uhm...
やっぱAZKiちゃんのね、Dream Trip、めちゃくちゃ良かった。
As expected, AZKi-chan's 'Dream Trip' was so good.
いや本当にね、歌ってくれてありがとう、AZKi先生！
No, really, thank you for singing it, AZKi-sensei!
はい、ここからはメアのターンということで、
Okay, from here on, it's MaiR's turn,
皆さん、まだまだ盛り上がれますか？
Everyone, can you get even more hyped?
まだまだ、いけますか！？
Can you still keep going!?
ありがとう！めっちゃ綺麗！コメントもね、ちゃんと見えてます。
Thank you! So beautiful! I can see the comments clearly too.
今日は、私たちとみんなだけの特別な日です。
Today is a special day just for us and everyone.
私たちだけ、みんなだけじゃなくて、
Not just us, not just everyone,
私たちとみんなで一緒に、最高の思い出、作ろうね！
but together, let's make the best memories!
オッケー？
Okay?
よし。
Alright.
それじゃあ、
Well then,
早速1曲目、歌いたいと思います。
I'd like to sing the first song right away.
聴いてください。
Please listen.
GROUND-ZERO。
GROUND-ZERO.
解き放て　世界へ
Set it free, to the world
LVS、ガンガン行こうぜー！
LVS, let's go all out!
解ききれない闇を行く
Going through the unbreakable darkness
希望の灯が消えたら　その時が幕開け
When the fire of hope goes out, that's the beginning
思い描いた何もかも
Everything I envisioned
その目で確かめるために　あの壁を打ち砕け Blow up!
To see it with those eyes, smash that wall, Blow up!
Hurry up
Wanna journey start now
魂と生命で Knock out!
With all my heart and soul, Knock out!
Kick back　確定も不確定も　抱えたままで
Kick back, keeping both certainty and uncertainty
目指す場所は　ひとつだけ
The place I'm aiming for is only one
- hope you take me out...
走り出せ　この手を伸ばせば
Start running, if I reach out this hand
夢に届くかな
Will I reach my dream?
胸に刻んだ今が　グラウンド・ゼロ
The present engraved in my heart is Ground Zero
焦げ付くほどに　勇気を燃やして
Burning courage enough to scorch
流れ星に重なる　軌道を描くよ
Drawing an orbit that overlaps with shooting stars
向かい風に傷付いても
Even if I'm hurt by the headwind
止まらずに進め！！
Proceed without stopping!!
Are you ready?
Let's get ready to break some wall
Come on!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1,
EXPLOSION!
未来を指した　あの場所から
From that place that pointed to the future
私のブレーキは　壊れていたんだ
My brakes were broken
クレッシェンドが止まらない　振り返らない
The crescendo doesn't stop, I won't look back
- can you set me free...?
解き放て　流した涙の
Set it free, of the tears I shed
欠片握りしめ
Clutching the fragments
駆け抜けてゆく　後悔なんて知らないまま
Running through, without knowing any regrets
信じることを　恐れたとしても
Even if I'm afraid to believe
秘めた情熱は　だって抑えきれないから
Because the hidden passion can't be suppressed
破裂しそうな　想いだけが
Only the feelings that are about to burst
揺るぎない真実
Are the unwavering truth
もっとずっと遠くへ
Further and further away
銀河さえ超えて
Beyond even the galaxy
未来まで
Until the future
この物語に　最高の結末を
The best ending to this story
願い遂げるために　すべてを捧げよう
I'll give everything to fulfill my wish
崩れ去る前に
Before it crumbles away
この手を伸ばせば　夢に届くかな
If I reach out this hand, will I reach my dream?
胸に刻んだ今が　グラウンド・ゼロ
The present engraved in my heart is Ground Zero
焦げ付くほどに　勇気を燃やして
Burning courage enough to scorch
流れ星に重なる　軌道を描くよ
Drawing an orbit that overlaps with shooting stars
向かい風に傷付いても
Even if I'm hurt by the headwind
止まらずに進め！！
Proceed without stopping!!
止まらずに進んで…
Go on without stopping...
あぁ…
Ah...
Wow!
サマー☆フロート
Summer Float
さあ最高！
Alright, the best!
もっと汗かきたいんじゃないの？
Don't you want to sweat more?
もっと暴れたいんじゃないの？
Don't you want to go wild more?
夏の曲やります。
I'll do a summer song.
サマー☆フロート！
Summer Float!
いけー！
Let's go!
絡まって弾けた光サマーデイズ
Tangled and bursting light, summer days
高く飛行機雲が煌めく空を描いた
High contrails drew a sparkling sky
高鳴る胸のその理由は
The reason for my racing heart
寄せては返す波のように
Like the waves that come and go
伝えられないんだ
I can't tell you
あぁ…
Ah...
重ねた言葉は二人で
The words we layered together
笑い合って解ける
Dissolve in our laughter
心夏の魔法にかかったみたいま…
It's like I'm under the magic of a heart's summer...
Take off Take off 空へ
Take off, take off to the sky
超えていこう Take off 風を
Let's go beyond, take off the wind
その手と手を合わせて
With our hands joined together
駆け出す夏の中を 今
Running through the summer, now
Take off Take off 空を
Take off, take off the sky
乗せて行こう 君と
Let's go together, with you
この手と手をつないだら
If I hold your hand
終わらない夏 混ざり合うメロディー
The endless summer, the mixing melody
Na na na...
眩しくてはにかむ笑顔サニーデイ
Bright and shy smiling sunny day
背中を押す南風 いたずらに服を揺らした
The south wind rustled my clothes mischievously
この夏にピース
Peace for this summer
その頬にキス
A kiss on that cheek
いつまでたっても
No matter how much time passes
落ち着かないんだ ああ…
I can't calm down, ah...
火照った身体は二人で
Our heated bodies together
ふざけあって解ける
Dissolve as we fool around
目線夏のリズムに溺れていたいま…
I want to drown in the rhythm of summer...
Take off Take off 空へ
Take off, take off to the sky
超えていこう Take off 風を
Let's go beyond, take off the wind
その手と手を握ったら
If I hold those hands
駆け出す夏の中を 今
Running through the summer, now
Take off Take off 空を
Take off, take off the sky
乗せて行こう 君と
Let's go together, with you
この手と手は離さない
I won't let go of these hands
目を閉じたら 始まるストーリー
If I close my eyes, the story begins
Na na na...
振り返る影は 遠く陽炎になって
The looking-back shadow becomes a distant heat haze
踊って揺らいで 結ばれてく 月明かりの下で
Dancing and swaying, being tied under the moonlight
夜に溶けてこのまま 二人で
Melting into the night, just like this, the two of us
今 Take off Take off 空へ
Now Take off, take off to the sky
超えていこう Take off 風を
Let's go beyond, take off the wind
その手と手を合わせて
With our hands joined together
駆け出す夏の中を 今
Running through the summer, now
Take off Take off 空を
Take off, take off the sky
乗せて行こう 君と
Let's go together, with you
この手と手をつないだら
If I hold your hand
終わらない夏 混ざり合うメロディー
The endless summer, the mixing melody
Na na na...
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
えー、2曲続けて聴いていただきました。
Um, you've just heard two songs in a row.
『グランドゼロ』と『サマーフロート』でした！
They were "Ground Zero" and "Summer Float"!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんな、拍手もありがとうございます。
Everyone, thank you for the applause as well.
じゃあね、次は、水を飲みたいと思います。
Well then, next, I'd like to drink some water.
あぁ。
Ah...
失った水分を、ここで取り戻すんだ。
I'm going to regain the moisture I lost here.
うー、おいしい！
Ooh, delicious!
あ、すごいすごいすごい。さっきもね、
Ah, wow, wow, wow. Earlier too,
見てたけどね、みんな水がすごいのよ。
I was looking, and everyone's water is amazing.
あー、すごいすごい。もうね、あの、
Ah, wow, wow. You know, um,
この会場がなんかダムになりかけてますね。
this venue is almost becoming a dam.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
みんなもちゃんと水分補給してね。
Everyone, make sure to stay hydrated too.
というわけで、まあ、今日なんですけど、
So, well, as for today,
まあ、配信イベントということで、
well, since it's a streaming event,
みんなは、どこで見てますか？
where are you all watching from?
どこで楽しんでくれてますか？
Where are you enjoying this from?
みんな、どこで見てるのかな？
I wonder where everyone is watching from.
まあね、あの、さすがにね、あの、
Well, you know, um, as expected, um,
すごいなんか、あの、すごいなんか、
it's really like, um, really like,
例えばなんだろう、
for example, what would it be?
炎に囲まれてとか、なんか、滝の下でとか、
Surrounded by flames, or maybe under a waterfall...
そういった窮屈な大変な場所では見ていないと思うんですけど。
I don't think you're watching in such cramped or difficult places.
え、トイレで見てるの？大丈夫？
Wait, you're watching in the bathroom? Are you okay?
まあ、みんなそれなりにね、あの、
Well, everyone is in their own way, um,
それなりのなんて言うんだろう、
in their own, how should I say,
自分なりのね、ホームで見てると思うんですけど。
watching from their own "home."
まあ、そこで見てくれてるなら、そこは、会場です！
Well, if you're watching there, then that place is the venue!
思いっきりね、悔いなく、
Please, with all your might and no regrets,
今日は楽しんでいってください。
enjoy yourselves today.
めあも楽しみます！
Mea will enjoy it too!
というわけで、まだね、めあは、2曲しか歌ってないので、
So, Mea has only sung two songs so far,
まだまだまだまだ、続きます！
so there's still much, much more to come!
ついてこれてますかー？
Are you keeping up?!
大丈夫？疲れてない？
Are you okay? Not tired?
オッケー！
Okay!
それじゃ、次も飛ばしていきますよ！
Then, I'm going to keep revving it up for the next one too!
聴いてください。
Please listen.
『夢の扉』！
"Yume no Tobira"!
夢の扉
The Door of Dreams
キラキラな 夜にはいつも
On sparkling nights, I always
考えてみるんだ
try thinking about it
心躍る 自分だけの
a heart-pounding future
未来を
that's mine alone
そしてまだ 見ぬ煌めく
And to the sparkling world
世界に
I've yet to see,
瞳閉じて 想いを馳せてみる
I close my eyes and let my thoughts wander.
挫けやしないよ
I won't be discouraged,
明日を止めずにさ
without stopping tomorrow.
何度も 挑戦だ
I'll try again and again,
明日への鍵を 探す旅
a journey to find the key to tomorrow.
夢の扉
Beyond the door of dreams
開いた先には
that has opened,
何があるんだ
what is there?
ワクワクがほら
Look, the excitement
止まらないんだよさぁ
won't stop, now
行こうか
let's go!
夢の扉
The door of dreams,
未来の誘いへ
towards the invitation of the future,
進んでゆけ
advance forward.
道のりは険しくないさほら
See, the path isn't steep,
そこに My World
there's My World.
まだ夜は 空見上げて
Still at night, looking up at the sky,
願ってみるんだ
I try making a wish
心から幸せな
for a future happy
未来を
from the bottom of my heart.
道に 迷う
When we get lost
一緒な時には
together at times,
流れ星を 道標にしよう
let's make a shooting star our guidepost.
自問自答 繰り返し
Questioning myself repeatedly,
答えを求めて
seeking the answer.
奏でるメロディは
The melody that plays
明日への鍵を探す旅
Is a journey to find the key to tomorrow
夢の扉 まだ見ぬ星のように
The door to dreams, like a star not yet seen
見えるだろうか
I wonder if it's visible?
ドキドキなんだよ
My heart is pounding
楽しみなんだよ
I'm so excited
早く行こうか
Shall we go quickly?
夢の扉 光の進む先へ
The door to dreams, towards where the light advances
進めてゆけ
Keep moving forward
終着点なんてないさ
There's no such thing as a destination
綴り出す
Start writing
THE NEW STORY
いざ行け！
Go for it!
夢の... 夢の扉はみんなのすぐ目の前にあるんだよ！
The door to... the door to dreams is right in front of everyone!
どんな時もMaiRが背中押すから
Because MaiR will always push you forward
悩んでる暇ないよ
No time to worry
いつでも MY NEW WORLD 見てよ
Always look at MY NEW WORLD
何度も挑戦だ
Challenge yourself again and again
明日への鍵を探す旅
A journey to find the key to tomorrow
夢の扉 希望に満ちている場所目指す
The door to dreams, aiming for a place full of hope
シナリオだってさ
Even a scenario
準備できたよ
Is ready
さぁ行こうか
Come on, let's go
夢の扉 光の誘う方へ
The door to dreams, towards where the light invites
進めてゆけ
Keep moving forward
道のり果てしくないさ
The path is not endless
ほらそこに
Look, right there
MY NEW WORLD
LAST V STANDiNG vol.3 AZKi x MaiR
星空のglitter
Hoshizora no Glitter
あぁ 思い煙る
Ah, the thoughts smolder
ガラス窓には冷たい雨
Cold rain on the glass window
あぁ こんな夜は
Ah, on a night like this
不思議な魔法を願うんだ
I wish for a mysterious magic
見上げた夜の空
The night sky I looked up at
君の声を星に混ぜて 掴めたら
If I could mix your voice with the stars and catch it
きらめいた星
A sparkling star
shooting star shooting star
届きそうだ
It seems like it could reach
溢れた涙
Overflowing tears
こぼれて星になる
Spilling over and becoming stars
遠く離れてても
Even if we're far apart
星が降る夜に ほら
On the night the stars fall, look
僕ら出会えたから
Since we were able to meet
隣のキミが笑っていられたら
If you could be smiling by my side
埋め尽くした流星は全部
All the shooting stars that filled the sky
星空のglitterだ
Are the glitter of the starry sky
たった一つだけ
Just one thing
伝えたいことがあるとして
If there's something I want to tell you
あぁ そんな時に
Ah, at a time like that
使える魔法があるんだ
There's a magic I can use
見上げた夜の闇
The darkness of the night sky I looked up at
僕の声を星に混ぜて 繋げたら
If I could mix my voice with the stars and connect them
きらめいた星
A sparkling star
shooting star shooting star
届きそうだ
It seems like it could reach
溢れた涙
Overflowing tears
こぼれて星になる
Spilling over and becoming stars
遠く離れてても
Even if we're far apart
星が降る夜に ほら
On the night the stars fall, look
僕ら出会えたから
Since we were able to meet
僕のキミが笑っていられたら
If my "you" could be smiling
埋め尽くした流星は全部
All the shooting stars that filled the sky
僕たちのglitterだ
Are our glitter
星が舞う夜に　ほら
On a night when stars dance, look,
僕ら出会えたから
since we were able to meet,
溢れた気持ち届いてほしいな
I want these overflowing feelings to reach you.
遠く離れてても...
Even if we're far apart...
星が降る夜に　ほら
On a night when stars fall, look,
僕ら出会えたから
since we were able to meet,
隣の君が笑っていられたら
if only you by my side could keep smiling.
埋め尽くした涙星は
The stars of tears that filled everything
全部　星空のglitterだ
are all the glitter of the starry sky.
閉ざした世界
In a closed-off world,
LAST V STANDiNG Vol.3 AZKi x MaiR
I can't control myself!
微かに聞こえる音
a faintly audible sound,
世界で二人きりみたいだ
it's like there's just the two of us in the world.
届きそうな手
Hands that seem almost within reach,
すれ違った心が
hearts that passed each other,
ちょっと痛むんだ
ache just a little bit.
ここで待って
Wait here,
wait here,
ここで待って
決められないままで
remaining unable to decide,
戸惑い溢れてしまうよ
confusion starts to overflow.
もう何度も繰り返した
I've repeated it so many times already,
こぼれた思いを数えて
counting the spilled thoughts.
何度も繰り返した
I've repeated it so many times,
世界　世界
the world, the world,
開くのを待っている
I'm waiting for it to open.
壊れた世界
In a broken world,
回り続ける針は
the hands that keep turning,
千切れた意識　繋いでいく
connect the torn consciousness.
刻んだ金属音
The engraved metallic sound,
鳴り響く心に
in my echoing heart,
ちょっと響くんだ
it resonates just a little bit.
ここで待って
Wait here,
wait here,
ここで待って
記憶繋げないままで
without being able to connect memories,
狂って壊れてしまうよ
it will go mad and break apart.
もう何度も繰り返した
I've repeated it so many times already,
神様に願いをかけて
making a wish to God.
何度も繰り返した
I've repeated it so many times,
世界　世界
the world, the world,
開くのを待っている
I'm waiting for it to open.
もう何もいらないから
Because I don't need anything anymore,
こぼれた思いは幻
the spilled thoughts are an illusion.
サヨナラ
Goodbye
何度も繰り返した
I've repeated it so many times,
世界　世界
the world, the world,
開くのを...
waiting for it to open...
もう何度も繰り返した
I've repeated it so many times already,
神様に願いをかけて
making a wish to God.
何度も繰り返して
Repeating so many times,
世界　世界
the world, the world,
開くのを待っている
I'm waiting for it to open.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最初に、お水を飲ませてください。
First, please let me drink some water.
（むせながら）むせちゃった。
(Coughing) I choked on it.
むせちゃった。
I choked on it.
はい、えーっと。
Yes, um...
夢の扉、星空のglitter。
Yume no Tobira, Hoshizora no Glitter.
そして、AZKiちゃんのオリジナル曲「I Can't Control Myself」を歌わせていただきました。
And I sang AZKi-chan's original song, "I Can't Control Myself."
このAZKiちゃんの曲なんですけど、
About this song of AZKi-chan's...
メアは実はカバーさせていただいておりまして、
I actually did a cover of it,
2年前... 2年前ぐらいにAZKiちゃんとコラボでね、
2 years ago... about 2 years ago, I did a collaboration with AZKi-chan,
「コラボ歌ってみた」を投稿した時に、
and when we posted a "Collab Utattemita" video,
同日、同日にメアもこのAZKiちゃんの曲のカバーをアップして、
on the same day, I also uploaded a cover of this song by AZKi-chan,
なんかその時は「あー、やったー！」みたいな。「あー、AZKiちゃんと歌えるんだ、嬉しい！」って、
and at that time, I was like, "Yay! I get to sing with AZKi-chan! I'm so happy!"
あの、メア、AZKiちゃん本当にシンガーとして尊敬してて、
Because I really respect AZKi-chan as a singer,
だからなんかそういう、そんな存在のAZKiちゃんと今日こうして
So, to be able to do this two-man live concert today
対バンライブをできて、本当に嬉しいです。
with AZKi-chan, who I look up to so much, I'm truly happy.
で、こんな素敵な場所に呼んでいただき、ありがとうございます。
And thank you so much for inviting me to such a wonderful place.
そして今日見てくれたみんな、一緒に楽しんでくれてるみんなも、本当にありがとうございます。
And to everyone watching today, everyone who's having fun with us, thank you very much.
えーっと、まあ、さっきも言ったんですけれども、今日はね、こう会場とかじゃなくて、
Um, well, as I said before, today, it's not at a physical venue,
配信でのイベントということで、
but a livestreamed event,
まあ、こういう世の中になってから、
well, since the world became like this,
自分の中で結構その「届ける」、誰かに届けるっていうことに関して、
I've spent a little over a year thinking a lot about "delivering,"
すごくたくさん考えた一年ちょっとでした。
about reaching out to someone.
まあ、新しいことを始めてみたりとかもしたんですけど、やっぱり自分には歌しかないって思ったし、
Well, I tried starting new things too, but I realized that for me, there's only singing,
そういう意味で、なんか色々、自分の好きなものとか、
and in that sense, it was a year of reconfirming the things I like
自分のやりたいこととかを再確認した一年でもありました。
and the things I want to do.
まあ世の中的にはなんかこう、ぴえん、っていう感じなんですけど、
The world is kind of in a "pien" (sad) state right now,
まあ、悪いことばっかりじゃないよっていうのをね、
but I hope that by me actually standing on this stage,
こうして実際にメアがステージに立つことで、みんなに届けられたらなって思います。
I can show everyone that it's not all bad things.
次でメアのパート最後の曲になるんですけど、
The next song will be the last one of my part,
次の曲はメア自身が作詞をさせていただいた曲です。
and I wrote the lyrics for this next song myself.
みんなへ届けたい思いを書いた曲です。
It's a song where I wrote about the feelings I want to deliver to everyone.
しっかり受け取ってくださいね。
Please make sure to receive them.
OK? ありがとう！
Okay? Thank you!
それじゃあ、最後の曲、あ、メアパート、メアソロパート最後の曲、聴いてください。
Now then, the last song—um, the last song of my solo part—please listen to it.
「君とミライ」
"Kimi to Mirai."
La la la ほら 君と今 響き奏でるよ
La la la, see, with you now, I'll ring out and play
あの空まで 届け
Reach up to that sky
声出して！
Let your voice out!
変わり映えのしない日常に 飽き飽きしてるその指先
To the unchanging daily life, those fingertips getting tired of it
そんな君が望んだ世界は きっとここにはない
The world that you wished for surely isn't here
妥協 手抜き 喧嘩ばっか 傷だらけでも
Compromise, cutting corners, only fighting—even if covered in wounds
あの日の笑顔の方が未来に近くて
The smile of that day is closer to the future
やっぱ 腫れちゃったまぶたは 君に合わない
After all, those swollen eyelids don't suit you
きっと昨日のミスも笑えたら 怖くないよね
Surely if we can laugh at yesterday's mistakes, it won't be scary, right?
飛ばせ ミライへ
Send it flying to the future
飛ばせ いつの日か
Send it flying, someday
夢見たステージ 行けそうな気がするじゃん！
The stage I dreamed of, I feel like I can make it there!
飛ばせ ミライへ
Send it flying to the future
飛ばせ いつの日か
Send it flying, someday
夢見た憧れ 音に変えて
Turn those dreamed-of longings into sound
La la la ほら 君と今 響き奏でるよ
La la la, see, with you now, I'll ring out and play
あの空まで 届け
Reach up to that sky
抱え込んだモヤモヤのせい 「一人じゃない」なんて言葉を
Because of the fuzziness I held onto, words like "You're not alone"
信じられない日もあったんだけれど わかるよ
there were days I couldn't believe them, but I understand
だって 挫けない才能が君にはある
Because you have the talent to never give up
もっと 夢色に咲いて ステージが早く見たいな
I want to see the stage bloom in dream colors more, I want to see it soon
飛ばせ 明日へ 飛ばせ いつの日も変わらない
Fly towards tomorrow, fly, the feelings that never change...
思いがこの胸にあるじゃん
They're in this heart of mine, right?
飛ばせ 明日へ 飛ばせ いつの日も変わらない
Fly towards tomorrow, fly, the feelings that never change...
気持ちをマイクに乗せて
Putting those feelings into the microphone
ラララほら 君と今 シンフォニー 奏でたら
La la la, see, if we play a symphony together now
手を繋いで行こう
Let's go hand in hand
繋いで行こう
Let's go together
そっと 閉じたそのマニュアルには 書いてない
It's not written in that manual you softly closed
ずっと 秘密の基地に置いてきた 譲れないもの
The things I've always kept in my secret base, things I can't give up
声に出して
Let's shout it out
飛ばせ 未来へ 飛ばせ いつの日か 夢見たステージ
Fly towards the future, fly to the stage I once dreamed of
行けそうな気がするじゃん
I feel like I can get there, right?
飛ばせ 未来へ 飛ばせ いつの日か 夢見た憧れ
Fly towards the future, fly, the admiration I once dreamed of
音に変えて
Turning it into sound
ラララほら 君と今 シンフォニー 奏でるよ
La la la, see, I'll play a symphony with you now
あの空まで届け
Reach for that sky
そこにいる君に 届け！
Reach for you right there!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとうございました！ 君と未来でした！
Thank you very much! That was "Kimito Mirai"!
えー最後の曲が終わったということで
Well, now that the last song is over...
あの方をお呼びしたいと思います。 みんな、いいですか？ いくよ？
I'd like to call that person over. Everyone, are you ready? Here we go.
せーの、AZKi先生ー！
Ready, set... AZKi-sensei!
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい、先生なんですか？
Yes, so I'm "Sensei" now?
もう先生になります。もう認めちゃう。
You're "Sensei" now. I'm making it official.
いやー本当によかった。なんかねあのねあのね、 AZKiのね、めあちゃんのね、大好きなとこ言っていいですか？
Wow, that was really great. Um, can I tell you what I love about you, Mea-chan?
え、何？
Eh, what is it?
あの曲間のMCがめっちゃ好き。
I really love your MCing between songs.
待って、それ聞いたら次からちょっと意識しちゃう。 ちょっと恥ずかしくなっちゃうんだけど。
Wait, now that I've heard that, I'll be too self-conscious next time. It's a bit embarrassing.
いやなんかさ、めあちゃんその歌ってるその勢いのままこうみんなにさ伝えるさ、
No, but Mea-chan, the way you convey messages with the same energy you have while singing,
この曲間のメッセージ性、みんな良くないですか？
isn't it great, everyone?
みんなわかる、わかる、わかるよね？
Everyone understands, right? Right?
先生！
Sensei!
ここテストに出ますよみたいな。 ここテストに出ますね。めあちゃんのいいポイント。
It's like "This will be on the test". This part definitely will. One of Mea-chan's best points.
先生、ありがとうございます。嬉しい。
Thank you, Sensei. I'm happy to hear that.
いや本当になんか、めあちゃんの歌を聴いてると、 なんか勇気というか元気というか、
Seriously, listening to Mea-chan's singing gives me courage and energy...
なんかすごい明るい気持ちをもらえます。
I get such a bright feeling from it.
みんなここテストに出ます。
Everyone, this will be on the test.
わかりました。カキカキ。メモメモ。
Got it. Scribble scribble. Taking notes.
あ、みんな、わかりみが、わかりみが。
Ah, everyone understands too.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
いや本当になんか元気になる、この曲？曲間？
It really makes you energetic, this song? Or the talk?
いやでも対バンって、そのぶつかり合うんだけど、 お互いにエネルギーを与え合ってる、なんか。
Well, in a versus live, you clash, but you also exchange energy with each other.
あ、確かに！それは思った。なんかだろう、 普段こう一人でライブやってるよりも...
Ah, definitely! I felt that too. It's different from performing solo...
めあちゃんがこんなに、こんなに力強く歌っているから、
Because Mea-chan is singing so powerfully,
AZKiももっと、もっと気合入れなきゃと。
AZKi feels like she has to sing with even more spirit.
え、嘘？めちゃくちゃ感化されておりますけれども。
Really? I'm feeling very inspired then.
はい、皆さんどうでした？ みんなコメントでぜひぜひ感想などなど。
So, how was it, everyone? Please leave your thoughts and comments!
ありがとう。あ、可愛い。赤青赤青。
Thank you. Oh, cute. Red and blue, red and blue.
あーすごい！赤青赤青のみんなハートをね、 めちゃめちゃいっぱい送ってくれて。
Wow, look at that! Everyone is sending so many red and blue hearts.
ありがとう、ありがとう。暑かった？
Thank you, thank you. Was it hot?
えらいえらい。えらいえらい。
Good job, good job.
よしよしよしよし。
There, there.
あ、すごい。ハート100点、100点、100点と。
Oh, look. 100 points, 100 points, 100 points for the hearts.
素晴らしい。いやーパワフルでした。
Wonderful. That was powerful.
お、嬉しい、ありがとう。最高！歌声のシナジーある！やったー！
Oh, I'm glad, thank you. "Awesome! Vocal synergy!" Yay!
いやもうこの衣装からね。もうスクショタイム始まってるから。
Even with these outfits. Screenshot time has already started.
二人揃うと...
When the two of us are together...
あぁ、いい感じのショットになってる。
Ah, it's becoming a great shot.
さぁ、みんな...
Come on, everyone...
100点！
100 points!
ありがとう、100点！
Thank you, 100 points!
撮影会始まっちゃった。
The photo shoot has started.
始まっちゃう。
It's starting.
はい、ということでですね、いや、改めて今日なんだろう...
Yes, so, well, once again for today, how should I say...
もうやってきたんですけれども、もうね、もう終盤なので、改めてちょっと...
We've come this far, and it's already the final stages, so once again...
早い！
So fast!
感想とかをメアちゃんに聞こうかな？
I'd like to hear MaiR-chan's impressions.
はい！
Yes!
どうでした？ どんなところがなんか良かった...
How was it? What parts did you like...
いや、まずね、もう今日本当に、あの、まず伝えたいことがあって...
Well, first of all, it was really fun today. There's something I really want to say first...
もう本当に、ありがとうございました！
Truly, thank you very much!
え、こちらこそ、本当に...
No, no, thank you! Truly...
メアちゃんがね、こう快諾していただかないと、このライブは開催されなかったので...
If MaiR-chan hadn't agreed to this, this live wouldn't have been held...
開催さ... あ、今来たばっかり勢が！
Held... Ah, the people who just arrived!
お、お、お！
Oh, oh, oh!
いや本当に、あの、さっきのMCでも言ったんだけど...
Truly, as I said in the MC earlier...
AZKiちゃん、本当にシンガーとして尊敬してて...
I really respect AZKi-chan as a singer...
えー、もうなんかそれを聞いて、なんかちょっとドキッとしちゃったんですけど。
Eh, hearing that made my heart skip a beat.
なんでよ！
Why!?
いや、だから、なんだろう。「あ、AZKiちゃんだ」と思って見ていたAZKiちゃんと...
So, how should I put it? Watching AZKi-chan and thinking "Ah, it's AZKi-chan"...
こういうふゅうに、対バンっていう形で...
And now, to be able to perform together in a "Taiban" format...
ね、共演することができて、本当に、自分にとってものすごく貴重な機会にもなったし...
Being able to perform together is a very precious opportunity for me...
いろんなものを学びました。
And I've learned many things.
えー、いや、AZKiもでも、本当にメアちゃんからたくさん、いろんなことを学んでおります。
Eh, no, AZKi has also learned a lot from MaiR-chan.
いや、でも、なんだろう、お互いその、結構活動はね、もう結構2年、3年とかで...
But, you know, we've both been active for about two or three years now...
そうだね。 やってきて、Vシンガーとして...
That's true. As V-singers...
そう、やってきて、なんか、こう、いろんなさ、いろんなことがあったじゃん。
Yes, we've been doing this, and there have been so many things, right?
感慨深い。本当に、いろんなことが、多分、活動してる中でさ...
It's deeply moving. Truly, in our activities...
楽しいことばっかりじゃなかっただろうし...
I'm sure it hasn't all been fun times...
あ、これ泣くやつですか？
Ah, is this the part where we start crying?
これ泣くやつですか？
Is this the crying part?
なんか、こうやってね、こうやって、今二人がここにステージに立てて、っていうことは...
So, well, the fact that the two of us are standing here on this stage right now...
本当に、もう、それだけでなんか、もう奇跡だなぁと思っていて。
It feels like a miracle in itself.
なんか、こうやって、ずっと活動を続けてなかったら、ここに二人立っていなかったし...
If we hadn't continued our activities, we wouldn't be standing here together...
そういう意味で、なんか、すごく、なんか、グッと...
In that sense, it's very... emotional...
いろんなものが重なって、いろんな思いが乗っかって、今日ができたっていう感じで。
So many things overlapped, so many feelings were involved, and that's how today came to be.
本当に。 そう、なんか、あと、そう、なんか一つ、あの、そう...
Truly. Yes, and one more thing...
今年か、今年、さ、AZKiも、こうやって、新衣装になって...
This year, AZKi got this new outfit...
そう！ で、メアちゃんもさ、その本当に近い日にちでね。
Yes! And MaiR-chan too, on a very close date.
そう、近い日にちで、この新、新... しかもなんか、いい感じ！
Yes, on a close date, this new... And it feels so right!
いい感じ。この口裏合わせたかのような。
It feels right. It's almost like we planned it!
本当に！ 本当に、これ、二人なんですけど。
Truly! Really, just the two of us...
なんか、そうやって、いろいろお互い活動してきて、こうやって今日二人がここで、ここで、こうやって立てているのを...
After being active in our own ways, for the two of us to be standing here like this...
みんなが、いや、こうやって、見てくれて、来てくれて、コメントしてくれて...
And for everyone to be watching us like this, coming here, commenting for us...
本当に、なんか、幸せな一日だったなぁと思います。
It's been a truly happy day.
分かる。
I know what you mean.
本当に、特別な一日を、みんなで作ったっていう感じで。
I feel like we all created this special day together.
いや、メアちゃんありがとう！ ありがとう！ ありがとう！ ありがとう！
MaiR-chan, thank you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
本当に、本当に、本当に。今日は皆さん、最後、最後じゃないけど...
Truly, truly, truly. Today, everyone, it's not the end yet, but...
いや、まだある！ まだあるんだけど！
There's still more! There's still more, but...
いや本当に、皆様お越しいただきまして、ありがとうございました！
Thank you all for coming today!
ありがとうございました！ ぜひぜひ、#LVS3で感想とかもね。
Thank you so much! Please share your impressions with #LVS3.
ぜひ、みんな、もう見に行きますからね。 めっちゃ！ もうあの、終わった瞬間に衣装脱いで...
We'll definitely go check them out. Definitely! After this ends, I'll take off my outfit...
シュルルルル〜って、エゴサしに行きますんで。
And go "shururu" to search for my name...
おお、早い早い！ ぜひぜひ、感想とかも呟いてくれると、嬉しいです。
Whoa, so fast! Please do tweet your impressions! It would make us happy.
はい！ ということで、ちょっとここで告知タイム〜！
Yes! So, it's time for some announcements!
はい！ ちょっと、AZKiの方から告知をさせてください。
Yes! Please let AZKi make an announcement.
えっ、一昨日と昨日と開催されました、えー、「不可解弐Q1:REBUILDING-形を失った世界で僕らは-」と、「不可解弐Q2:REBUILDING-世界は分岐するの-」...
The events held the day before yesterday and yesterday, "Fukakai 2 Q1: REBUILDING" and "Fukakai 2 Q2: REBUILDING"...
えー、アーカイブがですね、6月20日まで発売中です！ AZKiなんと、Q1に出させていただきました！
The archives are on sale until June 20th! AZKi actually appeared in Q1!
見たよ！ あ、ありがとう！
I saw it! Ah, thank you!
もう、なんか、やっぱり人の夢が叶った瞬間を見るっていいなって思って。
It's so nice to see someone's dream come true.
本当に、本当に、もうね、なんか夢だったのかなーっていう。
Truly, truly, it was like a dream.
そう、なんか、もう、いまだにちょっとふわふわしてるんですけど。
Even now, I'm still feeling a bit floaty.
やっぱ終わってからも？ そうそうそう。
Even after it's over? Yes, yes, yes.
なんだけど、なんか、そういうことがあったね、みんなにもね、観測してもらって。
So, please check it out everyone.
いや、本当に、なんか、夢を、なんか、みんな、自分が叶った...
Truly, I felt like my dream...
だってこうなってたもん、なんか。
Because you were like this.
メアちゃんが！ あ、やります？
MaiR-chan! Oh, shall I do it?
あ、そう。じゃあ、ちょっと、すいません、あの、本当に告知タイムで、すいません。
Oh, right. Sorry, sorry, it's announcement time.
AZKi先生のモノマネします！
I'll do an impression of AZKi-sensei!
カメラ映ってない！
The camera's not on you!
床のポーズを...
The floor pose...
床のポーズ！させるっていう。
Floor pose! Making me do that.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
いや、ずっとやりたかったんですよ、ここで。
I've actually always wanted to do it here.
やりたかったんだ。
You wanted to do it?
そう、ここのね、このステージでちょっと床になった出来事からですね、
Right, starting from that incident where I became the floor on this stage,
そこからなんとか、一昨日ライブをあのゲスト出演させていただきました、
from there, somehow, I was able to guest star in a live concert the day before yesterday,
こちらの「不可解弐」のアーカイブがZ-aNにて、えーと、6月20日までアーカイブ販売中なので、
the archive for 'Fukakai 2' is on sale at Z-aN until June 20th,
ぜひ「見逃した！」って方はもうぜひぜひ観測してほしいので、見ていただけると嬉しいです。
so if you missed it, I'd really love for you to go observe it. It would make me happy if you'd watch.
そして、なんと！
And, believe it or not!
21時から！
Starting from 21:00!
MaiRちゃんと！
With MaiR-chan!
メン限でアフタートークします！
We'll have an after-talk for members only!
イェーイ！集まれー！
Yay! Gather round everyone!
ということで、皆さんこの機会にぜひぜひメンバーシップの方もよろしくお願いいたします。
So, everyone, please take this opportunity to join the membership.
最速のアフタートークだぜ！ということで。
It's the fastest after-talk ever!
カモンカモン！MaiRちゃんも来てくれます。
Come on, come on! MaiR-chan will be there too.
はい。ということで、MaiRちゃんのお知らせはありますか？
Right. So, MaiR-chan, do you have any announcements?
私は今ちょっと言えることがまだないんですけど、あの、いろいろ準備中ではあるんで。
There's nothing I can say just yet, but I'm in the middle of preparing various things.
準備中。もうこれは皆さん、MaiRちゃんのYouTubeチャンネル、
Preparing. Well then, everyone, follow MaiR-chan's YouTube channel,
そしてMaiRちゃんのTwitterをフォローしてください。
and follow MaiR-chan's Twitter.
そう、このね、あの時期に、あの、お知らせされる内容をね...
Yes, for the details that will be announced in due time...
いいねいいね。概要欄に、皆さんのMaiRちゃんの...
Nice, nice. In the description, for everyone, MaiR-chan's...
チャンネルとTwitterを書いておりますので、ぜひぜひ登録してお知らせを待ってください。お願いします。
channel and Twitter are listed, so please subscribe and wait for the news. Please do.
はい。ということで、それでは本当に今日、最後の！
Alright. And now, for today's very last...
最後の曲か...。最後なんだ。
last song... It's the end.
もう一回やろう。ね、またやろう。ちょっともう一回やろう。
Let's do it again. Yeah, let's do it again. One more time.
Two days! Two days! やろうか。うん。
Two days! Two days! Let's do it. Yeah.
じゃあ今日はね、この曲で締めたいと思います。
Then for today, we'll wrap things up with this song.
はい。MaiRちゃん、じゃあ二人で、
Alright. MaiR-chan, then let's both,
タイトルコールしましょうか。はい！
do the title call. Okay!
せーの、ステップアップスーパースター！！
One, two, Step up Super Star!!
Step up step キラキラ ドキドキ 欠片を集めて Let's go!
Step up step, sparkling and heart-pounding, gather the fragments, let's go!
風は吹いたでしょ まっすぐ前を向いて
The wind has started to blow, right? Look straight ahead,
さあどこまでも走れ！
and run as far as you can go!
（ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ 最後だよ！ みんな盛り上がっていくよ！）
(Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! It's the last part! Let's get hyped everyone!)
Star いつも見上げてた 立ち止まったままで
Star, I was always looking up, standing still,
歩き出せずに ずっとずっとこのまま
unable to start walking, just staying this way forever.
Star 走り出さなくちゃ このままじゃ嫌だよ
Star, I have to start running, I don't want to stay like this.
本当の声が待ってるから
Because my true voice is waiting.
始まりはきっとね そんな些細なことだよ
The beginning is surely something trivial like that.
だってでもだけど ここに置いていこうよ
So let's leave all our 'buts' and 'howevers' here.
Step by step キラキラ ドキドキ 重ねて大きくなる
Step by step, sparkling and heart-pounding, they stack and grow bigger.
胸のときめきも 抑えきれなくて
Even the excitement in my chest, I can't hold it back anymore.
Day by day キラキラ ふわふわ 世界はありえない
Day by day, sparkling and fluffy, the world is unbelievable.
オールライト 覚悟決めれば 世界が光り出すよ
Alright, once you make up your mind, the world starts to shine.
さあどこまでも走れ！
Now, run as far as you can go!
（ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ まだまだいくよー！）
(Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Still going!)
Star 変わらないままで 泣き虫なままで
Star, staying just as I am, a crybaby just like before,
あの頃の声 抱きしめて
embracing my voice from back then.
描きたくなったの 次元も超える願いを
I wanted to draw a wish that even transcends dimensions.
飲み込んだ言葉 ここに吐き出しちゃおうか！
Let's pour out the words we swallowed right here!
Step by step キラキラ ドキドキ 集めて大きくなる
Step by step, sparkling and heart-pounding, gather them and grow bigger.
ワクワクのステージで 今 走り出して
On this exciting stage, now, start running.
Day by day キラキラ ふわふわ 絶好調を上げたい
Day by day, sparkling and fluffy, I want to reach my peak.
オーイエス 迷いはないよね これから目指す場所は
Oh yes, there's no more hesitation, the place we're aiming for from now on...
さあどこまでも走れ！
Now, run as far as you can go!
世界でいちばん？ (かわいいー！)
Number one in the world? (Kawaii!)
銀河でいちばん？ (かわいいー！)
Number one in the galaxy? (Kawaii!)
宇宙でいちばん？ (かわいいー！)
Number one in the universe? (Kawaii!)
AZKiとMaiRはスーパースター！
AZKi and MaiR are superstars!
世界でいちばん？ (だいすきー！)
Number one in the world? (Daisuki!)
銀河でいちばん？ (だいすきー！)
Number one in the galaxy? (Daisuki!)
宇宙でいちばん？ (だいすきー！)
Number one in the universe? (Daisuki!)
みんなのことがだいすきー！
I love you all so much!
今日は本当にありがとう！！
Thank you all so much for today!
しくじった朝も 間違えて泣いた夜も
The mornings you messed up, the nights you cried over mistakes,
全部君だけのものだ 愛しちゃおうか
it's all yours and yours alone. Let's embrace it all!
...やぁ！
...yah!
Step by step キラキラ ドキドキ 重ねて大きくなる
Step by step, sparkling and heart-pounding, building up and growing bigger
胸のときめきも 抑えきれなくて
Can't hold back the excitement in my heart
DAY BY DAY!!
Day by day キラキラでフワフワ 急展開ありえない
Day by day, sparkling and fluffy, unbelievable sudden developments
ALLRIGHT! 覚悟を決めるよ
All right! I'll make up my mind
前だけを見つめればほら
Look, if you just keep looking forward
輝いている 色鮮やかに 世界が光り出すよ
It's shining vividly, the world starts to light up
さあ どこまでも走れ！
Now, run as far as you can!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
ピンポンパンポーン
Ding-dong-dang-dong
本日は「LAST V STANDiNG vol.3」をご覧いただき、ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching "LAST V STANDiNG vol.3" today!
ぜひ感想を「#LVS3」で呟いてください！
Please share your thoughts using the hashtag "#LVS3"!
一つひとつ、大切に読んでいきます！
I'll read them all carefully, one by one!
AZKiも、めあちゃんも！
Both AZKi and Mea-chan!
はい！ということで！はい！
Yes! And so! Yes!
はい、今日はありがとうございましたー！
Yes, thank you so much for today!
ありがとうございましたー！楽しかったー！
Thank you so much! It was fun!
いやー、なんかあっという間に終わっちゃった。
Wow, it ended in the blink of an eye.
ね、早い。
Yeah, it was fast.
早い！
Fast!
はい、ということで、えっと21時からメン限のアフタートークがございますので。
Alright, so, we'll have a members-only after-talk starting from 21:00.
そこでね、思いの丈を...
There, we can talk about our feelings...
いや、いろいろ喋ろう！
Yeah, let's talk about all sorts of things!
いっぱい話したいことある！
There's so much I want to talk about!
みんなで、あの、語り合いたいと思います！
I want to chat with everyone!
今日はめあちゃん、ありがとうございました！
Mea-chan, thank you so much for today!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
本当に素敵な素敵な一日になりました。
It really became a wonderful, wonderful day.
おもいで...
Memories...
一日終わっちゃったけど...
The day is over, but...
これ寝たらまた朝に戻れるんですかね？
If I sleep now, can I go back to this morning?
あー、そう、そうですね。
Ah, right, I guess so.
そうですね。
That's right.
はい、ということで、じゃあまたどこかで二人と会ってください！
Alright then, please come and see the two of us again somewhere!
会ってください！
Please do!
はい、ではそれでは、まったねー！
Okay then, see ya!
まったねー！
See ya!
AZKi対バン企画
LAST V STANDiNG vol.3
#LVS3
【GUEST：MaiR】
AZKi Versus Project
LAST V STANDiNG vol.3
#LVS3
【GUEST: MaiR】